Just because they're a little older doesn't mean they've grown up.
Grown Ups 2 is a comedy film directed by Dennis Dugan.
Lenny has relocated his family back to the small
town where he and his friends grew up.
This time around, the grown ups are the ones learning lessons from their kids
on a day notoriously full of surprises—the last day of school.
Lenny Feder, played by Adam Sandler.
Eric Lamonsoff, played by Kevin James.
Kurt McKenzie, played by Chris Rock.
Marcus Higgins, played by David Spade.
Roxanne Chase-Feder, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Deanne McKenzie, played by Maya Rudolph.
Grown Ups 2 is a 2013 American comedy film directed by Dennis Dugan, written by Adam
Sandler, Fred Wolf, and Tim Herlihy, and produced by Sandler and Jack Giarraputo.
It serves as a sequel to the 2010 film Grown Ups and features Sandler, Kevin James, Chris Rock, David Spade, Salma Hayek, Maya Rudolph, Maria
Bello, and most of the cast members reprising their roles from the first film, alongside Nick Swardson, who joins the cast.
Lenny (played by Sandler) moves his family back to his
hometown, where he reunites with his old friends.
Together, they face bizarre situations and new
enemies in the form of a local fraternity.
Produced by Sandler's production company Happy Madison Productions and distributed by Sony Pictures
Releasing through its Columbia Pictures label, Grown Ups 2 was released on July 12, 2013.
It was panned by critics but grossed $247 million on an $80 million budget.
It was nominated for nine Razzies at the 2014 Golden Raspberry Awards.
The film explores themes of friendship, journey
in the past, cliff, past, sequel.
The tone is lighthearted.